[Crazy_Watson_sent SoundNodeWave]
bMature=False
bManualWordWrap=False
bSingleLine=False
SpokenText="You will be sent to a medical institute where you will receive the best treatments to facilitate your full rehabilitation."
Subtitles[0]=(Text="You will be sent to a medical institute where you will receive the best treatments to facilitate your full rehabilitation.")
Comment=""

[Parano_Watson_drug SoundNodeWave]
bMature=False
bManualWordWrap=False
bSingleLine=False
SpokenText="I can attest that your medication affected your judgement. You will not recall, but it caused you to temporarily lose control."
Subtitles[0]=(Text="I can attest that your medication affected your judgement. You will not recall, but it caused you to temporarily lose control.")
Comment=""

[Parano_Watson_help SoundNodeWave]
bMature=False
bManualWordWrap=False
bSingleLine=False
SpokenText="Mister Garrow, please do not be alarmed, we only wish to help you. You were under an intolerable stress but it is over now…"
Subtitles[0]=(Text="Mr. Garrow, please do not be alarmed, we only wish to help you. You were under an intolerable stress but it is over now…")
Comment=""

[Parano_Watson_not SoundNodeWave]
bMature=False
bManualWordWrap=False
bSingleLine=False
SpokenText="Do not distress yourself. Prison is clearly not a suitable environment for you."
Subtitles[0]=(Text="Do not distress yourself. Prison is clearly not a suitable environment for you.")
Comment=""

[Parano_Watson_suffer SoundNodeWave]
bMature=False
bManualWordWrap=False
bSingleLine=False
SpokenText="You are suffering from an acute form of melancholia, but you can and will be cured. All you need is rest and detoxification. I will take care of every detail."
Subtitles[0]=(Text="You are suffering from an acute form of melancholia, but you can and will be cured. All you need is rest and detoxification. I will take care of every detail.")
Comment=""

